<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Skagit Life</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Skagit Life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Poems</title>
      <link>/post/2020/04/23/two-poems/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/04/23/two-poems/</guid>
      <description>Tell all the truth but tell it slant — (1263) BY EMILY DICKINSON  Tell all the truth but tell it slant — Success in Circuit lies Too bright for our infirm Delight The Truth’s superb surprise As Lightning to the Children eased With explanation kind The Truth must dazzle gradually Or every man be blind —  Found from ref in this sermon by Richard Rohr.
  blessing the boats BY LUCILLE CLIFTON  (at St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>A presumptuous and rude blog about data, existence, God, R, music, and other1 things that are typed out due to the vibrations emanating from my brain 2.
It will soon become extremely successful, since I plan to model it after MacBeth&#39;s characterization of life itself 3.
I live in the Skagit Valley, which explains the domain name.
  adding to this list is now causing me anxiety &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
 The views and opinions expressed on this site are those of the author&#39;s brain and do not necessarily reflect the official policy or position of the author 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Websters dictionary defines “about” as:
 about, adverb: reasonably close to
 which I thought1 would be more relevant tbh.
I’m not so sure about this whole new trend to “do a blog” about “things” I am “interested” in 2 to “try to impress” the imagined beings who may click on something that commands their computer to render this3. It seems presumptuious and rude.
In conclusion, this is a place where patterns are stored on a server due to the vibrations of my brain 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There may be a blog post here someday</title>
      <link>/post/2020/04/01/not-a-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/04/01/not-a-blog-post/</guid>
      <description> But not today.
seriously, its not.
I’m just trying to plot something to see if it works.
like this 1
 Figure 1: hmmm.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 in Skagit Valley, Wa</title>
      <link>/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/covid/</guid>
      <description>Total daily counts of covid-19 cases, hospitalizations and deaths reported by Skagit Public Health.
     Cases include total confirmed and presumptive positives, which means that a private lab reported a positive test.
 Hospitalized are people with positive tests who were hospitalized at any point during their illness.
  The first case in Skagit Valley was reported on March 10, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>