<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Skagit Life</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Skagit Life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets make a Sankey!</title>
      <link>/post/2020/04/18/faithlife-theological-favorites-sankey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/04/18/faithlife-theological-favorites-sankey/</guid>
      <description>In many ways1, I am a simple man. If I see an opportunity to make a Sankey, I get my Sankey on. Here’s the plan2.
The Plan (explain plan here)3  Ok, now to jump in and start coding!
library(ggplot2) #priorities library(tidyverse) library(ggthemes) library(instaR) #devtools::install_github(&amp;quot;pablobarbera/instaR/instaR&amp;quot;) … okay after horsing around for a bit trying to get an access token for Instagram’s API and being very sketchily asked to pretend to be a “business”, upload a pic of my “app icon” and makeup something official sounding to put as my “privacy policy url”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Websters dictionary defines “about” as:
 about, adverb: reasonably close to
 which I thought1 would be more relevant tbh.
I’m not so sure about this whole new trend to “do a blog” about “things” I am “interested” in 2 to “try to impress” the imagined beings who may click on something that commands their computer to render this3. It seems presumptuious and rude.
In conclusion, this is a place where patterns are stored on a server due to the vibrations of my brain 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Websters dictionary defines &amp;ldquo;about&amp;rdquo; as:
 about, adverb: reasonably close to
 which I thought1 would be more helpful in this context tbh.
I&#39;m not so sure about this whole new trend to do a blog about topics I am interested in 2 to try to impress a handful of imagined beings who may click on something that commands their screen to render this3. The whole idea just seems presumptuous and rude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There may be a blog post here someday</title>
      <link>/post/2020/04/01/not-a-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/04/01/not-a-blog-post/</guid>
      <description> But not today.
seriously, its not.
I’m just trying to plot something to see if it works.
like this 1
 Figure 1: hmmm.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 in Skagit Valley, Wa</title>
      <link>/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/covid/</guid>
      <description>Total daily counts of covid-19 cases, hospitalizations and deaths reported by Skagit Public Health.
     Cases include total confirmed and presumptive positives, which means that a private lab reported a positive test.
 Hospitalized are people with positive tests who were hospitalized at any point during their illness.
  The first case in Skagit Valley was reported on March 10, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>